Greem Lee

Software Engineer





in linkedin.com/in/greem-jellyfish-hai-pa-lee/

A multidisciplinary creator with a background in installation, conceptual art, techno and alt k-pop music. Utilizes code as a medium to communicate and provide services. Possesses 2 years of freelance web dev experience with a focus on profit increase and efficiency of use. Looking for a full stack or a frontend dev role.

Technical Skills

Languages JavaScript(ES6), CSS, SASS, HTML, Ruby
Libraries/Framework ReactJS, Redux, Rails, PostgreSQL, SQL, D3, Observable, Semantic UI, Jest
Tools Git, Heroku, Netlify, Figma, Sketch, Wordpress, Wix, Shopify, Responsive CSS Grid

Experience

Freelance Software Engineer Handsome Hand

New York, NY | Nov 2020 - Current

- Delivering 25 ReactJS components on-time and under budget for clients.
- Reducing deployment time by 2x through implementation of Netlify.

Volunteer Software Engineer Femmecubator

New York, NY | Jan 2021 - Current

Collaborating with UX/UI and the engineering team to add checkboxes for user sign up.

Freelance Wix Web Developer One World Acupuncture New York, NY | Mar 2019 - Apr 2020

- Integrated Wix payment platform enabling patients to make appointments with credit card and paypal.
- Designed a dynamic web page, optimized navigation and search engine optimization that resulted in the first result in google search, a 500% increase in visits and a 300% increase in profitability over 6 months.

Freelance Wix Web Developer Sensei Fine Arts

New York, NY | Oct 2018 - Mar 2019

- · Designed and coded application components with responsive pages for users to navigate gallery's data.
- Gathered requirements from client and proposed product solutions to drive revenue.

Software Engineering Projects

Hae Nyeo Spa Appointment website | github | demo video

- Leveraged React Router and Redux to allow users to book and update spa appointments without refresh.
- Added interactive floating SVG objects for a playful user experience.
- Improved deployment time by 4x and practiced CD by using Netlify.
- Managed GitHub repositories and permissions and project-managed using agile processes.

M-Wine Tasting Review website | github

- Built an interactive sunburst wine tasting chart using D3 and Observable so users can explore and record their sublime wine tasting experience.
- Leveraged React JS to allow users to dynamically add reviews without page refresh.
- Decreased time spent on visual design by 20 hours by adding Semantic UI.

Growth Mindset Quote website | github | demo video

- Built a full stack web app using JS, Ruby and deployed on Github.io to allow users to explore the web page.
- Achieved responsive design on mobile and 5 different desktop browsers writing custom and dynamic CSS.
- · Defined PostgreSQL schemas for users, quotes, author, images, and likes.
- Reduced Heroku costs by \$25 per month through adding a custom CSS loader.

Education

Flatiron School Software Engineering

Brooklyn, NY | Apr 2020 - Sep 2020

Received full scholarships from NYC Tech Talent Pipeline for excellence in computer science

New York University Steinhardt School, B.F.A. Studio Art Dean's List. Awarded academic scholarship

New York, NY | May 2014